

## Producer / Project Manager





acjh13@gmail.com



Highly adaptive and multi-disciplined Producer / Project Manager with a technical and design background. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

## **Industry Experience**

**Junior Producer** | Lionfish Studios Pte Ltd – *Various Projects*Mar 2021 – Present

- Managing communications between development team and stakeholders
- Managing in-house and outsource development teams
- Assisting in overseeing <u>project milestones and releases</u>
- Coordinating project development with <u>multiple cross-functional</u> teams
- Leading company-wide transition to a <u>Sprint-based development cycle</u>

**Production Intern** | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - *Final Fantasy Brave Exvius* Sept 2020 – Feb 2021

- Maintained event lists for content updates with <u>Google Sheets</u> and <u>Confluence</u>
- Responsible for Design team's <u>Sprint Planning</u> and follow ups with <u>Jira</u>
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to streamline and <u>automate</u> production workflows

## On-Campus Experience

**Teaching Assistant** | DigiPen Singapore – *Game Production Class* Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

Advised ~10 student teams on project management and game production

# **Academic Projects**

## **Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer**

Kindred | Sept 2019 – June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- <u>Communicated</u> game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted <u>Agile</u> methodology with weekly <u>Scrum</u> meetings and <u>Kanban</u> boards
- Created <u>cross-department workflows</u> for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

## **Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer**

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Worked with lecturers and team members to resolve conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

## Education

# Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Game Design

DigiPen Institute of Technology, Singapore Sept 2017 – Apr 2021

- Dean's Honour List, Fall '19
- Exchange Student DigiPen Redmond, Summer '19

## Skills

#### **Soft Skills**

Effective Communication Team Management Problem Solving Detail Oriented Conflict Resolution Project Ownership

#### **Management Methods**

Agile Scrum Kanban

## **Management Software**

Jira Trello
Confluence HacknPlan
Slack Discord
Google Suite Microsoft Suite

## **Software & Tools**

Git / SVN Microsoft Office
Visual Studio Visual Studio Code
Unity Unreal Engine

Custom Game Engine(s)

### **Programming Languages**

C / C++ C#
Python JavaScript
Rust Lua

### **Spoken Languages**

English (Native) Mandarin (Limited)

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!